What you doing?
You fucked with us, Charlie.
I did not, sir.
Reggie Ledoux.
I don't even wanna know that freak, man!
Y'all didn't ask nothing about Reggie!
Fuck, man. My...
My wife just died.
Ex-wife!
You had Reggie Ledoux
take her out, didn't you?
- No.
- Hmm?
- What are you talking about, man?
Reggie? Put her out there
with them antlers on?
You have Reggie do it? Hmm?
What are you talking about?
Reggie Ledoux did this?
Reggie Ledoux.
Reggie motherfucking Ledoux did this?
Fucking shit! Let me out, man!
Let me out! Fuck, man!
- Hey, Charlie.
Motherfucking sick fuck!
We're not gonna give you the Oscar,
no matter how hard you try.
Oh, fuck you, man! You don't know me!
You don't know what I been through!
What are you talking about? You talk to me!
Ledoux knew about her, right?
You talk about her to him?
Yeah, man. Yeah!
The way you do sharing a house.
Yeah, you talk pussy.
Talk scores. That's what you do.
Showed him pictures of her'?
Yeah, I guess so. Yeah.
I had stuff she gave me
when I first went down.
Stuff for me to look at.
You know, like Polaroids.
He was a big guy.
A lot bigger than you.
Did you tell me you didn't get along?
No. I mean, I did. Most part. You got to.
You sharing a house, like I'm saying.
I mean, he gets you high, man, but
he's creep. I ain't wanna know him.
Tell me about Ledoux. How's he "creep"?
He's a cook, you know. Like a chemist.
Used to make shit out of kitchen stuff,
cook down cleansers and whatnot.
Used tater skins and fry grease
to make hi-test sour mash.
He got mad knowledge for that shit,
but I don't know, man.
He talk like a short-eyes. Like somethin'.
How you mean?
He wouldn't talk that shit up in here.
No, man, he didn't. Like,
me and him at night.
Blasted up on one of his mixes.
He could brew some shit up,
put you up out your head, man.
That's a big deal in here.
Fuck, man, that's a big
deal out there, too.
So, uh...
What kinda shit was he talking?
He said that there's this place down south
where all these rich men
go to, uh, devil worship!
He said that, uh...
They sacrifice kids and whatnot.
Women and children
all got murdered there and...
Something about some place called Carcosa
and the Yellow King.
He said there's all these, like,
old stones out in the woods.
People go to, like, worship.
He said, uh...
He said there's just so much
good killing down there.
Reggie got this brand
on his back, like in a spiral.
He says that's their sign.
What-the-fuck-ever, you understand?
I don't listen to the man, but he's big.
So I don't tell him shut
the fuck up, neither.
You remember any buddies
he ever talked about?
See, we checked the records here,
and he had never had any visitors.
We both know Tyro Weems.
Tyrone might could tell you where he's at.
Look, man. Reggie is crazy. Like, for real.
Had to be tough.
Living with somebody spouting
insane shit in your ear.
All day long.
You gonna get me something
for what I told you just now?
Parole board nod. Fair's fair.
Hey. Hey!
You think 'cause I talked to him
about Dori that
I might have got her killed?
You probably had something to do with it.
I don't think you should have
shown him those pictures.
Do you?
We need to find this Tyrone Weems.
See what he knows about Ledoux.
HART; Yeah.
You didn't have to tell
him it was his fault.
Guy was already low.
Yeah, he asked about his end first.
Parole board.
So?
So, fuck him.
You funny, Marty.
The shit you get soft about.
I wanted every member
of that family that I could find.
Turns out,
there weren't any.
You know how weird that is in Louisiana?
A cousin, Dewall,
was not on paper,
except for a truckers license.
Ledoux had turned into a ghost
from the time he skipped parole check.
Tell me, young studs,
what would you do
when you hit a wall like that?
Responding to the complaint,
I approached the house.
Seeing that the screen door was broken
and the inner door ajar,
I felt that entrance complied
with standard procedure.
Upon entering the domicile,
I noticed what appeared to be marijuana
and a white powder on the coffee table.
Hey, Martin!
- We don't have to talk, Lisa.
- Like hell we don't.
You don't get to do
what you did to me last week.
Look, I'm sorry. I was hurt and real drunk.
Talk to me now.
Okay.
I wish you a great life,
and good luck with your new friend.
You philandering fucking asshole.
Hey! There is no pageant to perform. Okay?
Your disappointment is irrelevant.
You don't get to act like that, Marty.
Or like this.
I've acted as nice as I'm gonna,
and I don't wanna
have this conversation again.
You need to respect me, Marty.
This is respect.
Rust figured a connection
with an earlier death,
suspicious, Rianne Olivier,
led us to the DB's old boyfriend,
Reginald Ledoux, 35.
Statch rape charge against a 12-year-old,
acquitted for lack of testimony.
Did a bid for manufacturing meth and LSD,
which fits the tox screen for Lange.
And his old cellmate
was Lange's ex-husband.
He showed him
some cheesecake pictures of her.
From what we know about him,
the way he talked,
he sounds like he's real good for it.
No line on any of his people.
Swamp folk, dug in off the grid.
We are tracking a KA, Tyrone Weems.
He's in the sheets that we passed out.
Any questions?
I didn't think so.
Let's get to work.
You Theresa Weems? Tyrone Weems' mom?
Tyrone hadn't been around in a while.
You know, a few months.
We got in a fight,
'cause he sold my microwave.
What about his friends?
You know where they hang out?
I don't know. He dated this girl,
Kelsey, for a little while.
Kelsey,
when's the last time you saw Tyrone?
Months. We been broke up.
I don't ever hear from him.
I don't want to.
I heard he got Shawnda Miller pregnant.
So, do you have his address, phone number'?
Look, I really wish I could help you,
but I can't. I have to get back to work.
Hey!
You know that gal back there?
She got a man'? Manager'?
Hey, do I gotta pull my badge?
Hey, we run clean here.
How you gonna run
when you're shut down six months
for a grand jury inquiry?
Why are you making me say this shit, man?
Do you know her old man?
Yeah, he came around collecting from her.
Boss kicked him out
for trying to sell crys to the girls.
That's about a month ago.
- Look familiar?
- Yeah, that's him.
- He ever pick her up?
- Yeah.
Went to work on Tyrone Weems.
Known associates, family.
Had a little leeway with Quesada,
now that we had a suspect.
Fuck!
Fuck! Fuck! God damn it!
- Lisa.
- How does it feel?
I told you, you can't
treat people like this.
Listen, I just need to know
exactly what you told her.
You mink ifs okay what you do?
All of you think it's okay
you treat your wives the way...
You treat women the way...
You're fucking liars and bullies
and this is what you get.
This is what you get.
I have children. You blew up my life!
You fucking whore!
What'd you just call me?
What'd you just call me,
you fucking wet-noodle,
whiskey-dick faggot fuck?
I will skull fuck you, you bitch!
Hello, Jake?
Jake, is this you?
Marty.
Ls Maggie there?
That's none of your goddamn business.
Jake, I know she's there.
I know she's there. Put her on the phone.
I know what you did, Marty.
Leave her alone, you fucking asshole.
- Jake... I...
- You're not hearing me.
I don't know what she told...
Leave her atone.
And I know we haven't always
seen eye to eye...
You're goddamn right
we've never seen eye to eye.
Just please, put her on the phone for me.
No. You're no damn good, Marty.
She deserves better, and don'!
Cal? here again.
Jake...
How many exes you guys have?
I mean, that's what I'm talking about.
Did I make some mistakes?
Yes.
You know the detectives curse?
Solution was right under my nose,
but I was paying attention
to the wrong clues?
- See you later.
- Bye.
- Damn!
- Police.
Fuck.
Reggie Ledoux. Where is he? Now.
That's what this is about?
Man, why didn't you say so...
Where the fuck is he?
I heard he still cook.
I heard he stopped selling
after he did his bit.
He only cook for one client now.
Who?
Some bike gang.
They buy all his product.
Bulk order. No mess.
I heard this at the clubs is all.
Reggie don't distribute no more.
Which bike club?
Iron Heroes, or some shit.
Iron Crusaders.
I don't keep up with them gear heads.
- Iron Crusaders. You sure'?
- Yep. Them ones.
What I heard,
Reggie cook their loads, and that's all.
Close your eyes and count
to 100, if you can.
Go.
One.
- Two.
- Louder!
Three!
Four!
Five!
Listen, I talked
to Weems, and Ledoux is cooking
for some motorcycle gang out of Texas.
Iron Crusaders.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
You're sure he said Iron Crusaders?
Fm sure he said Iron Crusaders.
So, we'll...
We'll chase that tomorrow, yeah?
What are you doing right now?
Right now, Pm busy.
Well, as! recall,
I had to take some personal time.
See my dad.
I mean, this is, like, what?
Seventeen years ago?
I mean, yeah.
You're gonna have to understand if my
memory hadn't sharpened in the interim.
- Fran, stay by the phone.
- I will.
Maggie, can I talk to
you for just a second?
No. I'm working graveyard.
Girls are with my mom and dad.
It's all in the note, Marty.
Okay. But give me a chance to...
She came to my home.
Our daughters saw her.
You lying fuck. You stupid, lying fuck.
Jesus Christ. Listen to me, Mags.
I meant everything I said the other night.
Every word.
- I stopped...
- Oh, my God.
You think your betrayal's
removed by its interruption?
She was disgusting. You're disgusting.
- You can't fix this.
- Listen to me. God, listen to me.
Get your hands off me.
Okay. I've been...
I've been a mess. Rattled.
My...
- Just, my dad dying...
- Oh, my God.
- That was a year ago.
- And drinking...
I don't give a shit
about your goddamn feelings.
You need to get out of our lives, Marty.
Me and the girls. Read the note.
It's all there.
You can't come home.
- You don't mean that. You don't mean that.
- Yes. Yes, I do.
Listen, I...
You are not gonna break up
my fucking family, okay?
- Get out of here right now.
- No!
Excuse me. You all right, Maggie?
Sir, I suggest you leave.
Everything's fine, Doc. I'm state police.
I appreciate that,
but are you here in that capacity now,
as law enforcement?
You don't want to do this.
Get your hands off me! God damn it!
Call your commanding officer!
You're making a scene, Many!
No. There is no scene unless
mall patrol here makes one.
I am calmly discussing
a private matter with my wife.
You're private in a pretty public way, man.
Easy. Easy.
It's none of your fucking business.
No, it's none of my
business, but we got work.
Marty, I got a line on Ledoux.
I got it right fucking now. I need you.
Can we leave this shit until later?
I love you, honey.
I ain't giving up.
Come on.
We can get to Ledoux.
All right? But it's gonna be dirty.
I just need her to give me another shot.
If I could just get another shot.
Listen, can I tell you something?
Yeah.
This is none of my business.
I don't wanna hear it.
Right. I'm sorry.
You total shit.
You know, this is part on you.
You know, you can't just slide into
my life creating tensions...
What, I make you tap some bimbo,
looks like a young Maggie?
I make you flaunt that shit?
Fuck, that night at the Longhorn,
you were so obvious, man, checking her out.
And she looked crazy enough
to have followed you there.
With all the dick swagger you roll,
you can't spot crazy pussy?
I fucked up.
Just...
I like something wild. I always did.
I just...
It feels like it smoothes out
the other parts of my life...
Listen, Marty. One more time.
It's none of my fucking business.
Fuck.
Look.
We got a job to do.
Off-book.
It's the only play I can think of.
I got to straighten out things
with the family. I gotta fix it.
That bike club. I know 'em.
Had deals with 'em when
I was working narco.
We can get to that motherfucker Ledoux.
So, enough with the self-improvement,
penance, hand-wringing shit.
- Let's go to work.
- You think you're...
Fuck!
Hell of a bedside manner you got, Rust.
You know being stupids
different than calling in sick,
and this is a bar, not a fucking bedside.
A friend in need.
Every time I think you hit a ceiling,
you just keep raising the bar.
You are like the Michael Jordan
of being a son of a bitch.
That's it. Come on.
You're really gonna love this jacket I got.
Holy shit!
You visit a lot of gun shows?
No, it's just some stuff I kept
just in case some work came back on me.
These boys Ledoux deals to,
they're out of East Texas.
I worked 'em when I was DEA task force.
They know you're 5-0?
Nope.
I wasn't sure, so I checked
with my old handler.
As far as my cover goes,
I took three slugs in a DEA shoot-out
at the port of Houston.
Anybody gives a shit, figures I'm dead.
Major said the task force
used to call you Crash.
I'm gonna have to take
some personal time on this, Marty.
A couple of weeks.
Got to get out there and get seen,
drop some lines.
I mean, badges ain't gonna
get us near these people,
so the plan is we make 'em an offer.
Get a line on their supplier.
Confirm it's Ledoux.
Bring him in.
Then once we're out there,
all right, it's just you and me on this.
I don't like that.
What happens if they clock you're not you?
Mmm.
No, I can't do what I need to do
if we got watchdogs.
Besides, like you said, Quesada'd pull me.
The stakes ain't that high anyway.
I get found, I take a bullet to the head.
This cartel I worked on the border,
they had this routine.
They'd duct tape you to a chair
that was bolted to the floor.
Use a couple rolls,
make sure you couldn't
budge a fucking inch.
And then, they'd cut around your face,
grip your scalp, yank down.
Rip your face off.
Hmm.
Then they put a mirror in front of you,
so you can get a good look at yourself.
Then they cut your dick and your balls off,
shove 'em down your throat
until you bled and choked out
while you were watching.
So, as far as high stakes go,
bullet to the head,
it ain't that.
Hey.
You sure you wanna do this?
Not exactly.
You realize you got
a upstairs here, right?
What is that?
Ink and cayenne.
Irritates the skin, looks contused.
How long did they have you out there,
working the corridor?
- Almost four years.
- Four?
What the hell.
UCs ain't supposed
to do more than 11 months.
Yeah, but I had fucked up on the job,
and they could do
whatever they wanted with me.
That's a long time being like that.
I need a good story to move fast,
and I think I got one.
All I need now is some good coke.
Where you gonna get that?
Don't worry about it.
So you got a suspect,
and you take a leave of absence?
Yep.
Like I said, to see my pops.
Had leukemia.
Hey, Favre.
Can I get the evidence key from you?
Yeah.
- Heard you were taking time.
- Yeah, leaving tonight.
- Sign the log.
- Yep.
You supposed to see both eyes in this one?
They really should have
a better system for this.
We looked at
your old partner's history.
And coincidences keep mounting, Detective.
Oh, coincidences. Like what?
Well, I don't know if
it would qualify as coincidence,
but near as we can tell,
his pops never had leukemia.
No hospital records of that.
Fact' nobody in that town in Alaska
seen Travis Cohle in more than 30 years.
That it?
You still angry at him? Your pops?
No.
He's dead.
You were, though?
I mean, why you two didn't talk.
We never really liked each other.
There's a difference.
He was in 'Nam.
Met my mother on leave in Galveston.
The time he came back, I was two.
She dumped me on him, then she hauled ass,
and he and I moved to Alaska.
He was a survivalist, I
guess you'd call it.
Had some pretty fucking strange ideas.
Oh, there's nothing like
the night sky out there, though.
I couldn't handle the cold,
so I headed back to South Texas,
'cause all I could remember was
at least it never got cold.
My old man always made
like I let him down that way.
Said I had no loyalty.
A clean break is best now,
while they're still young.
Look, it's none of my business, okay.
But I do need him to watch my back on this.
This is how you all get warped.
You always shortchange the wrong things.
Shortchange.
- Mmm-hmm.
What else?
He wanted me to pass a tide
of apologies of which I'll skip.
And he wants to see the girls
if you can make time for it.
Kids are the only thing
that matter, Maggie.
They're the only reason for
this whole man-woman drama.
I'm sorry.
What are you suggesting, exactly?
Just that people fuck up.
We age.
Men, women, it's not supposed to work,
except to make kids.
So if you could imagine
Marty's behavior
as an expression of weakness,
Pain'
you'd see that it's not about you.
So, end of the day,
you duck under rationalization.
Same as any of 'em.
You must've been a great husband.
People been seeing me around
for about a week.
Guy I used to run with,
he wants to meet me tonight.
Now, if I can get him alone,
we snatch him up, work him over,
maybe get to Ledoux.
- Okay. Great.
- All right.
Listen...
Phone's fully charged.
And remember, it's real simple.
Green answers. Red hangs up.
- I'm the only one that's gonna be calling.
- All right.
- Keep it charged.
- Yeah.
Listen, how was she? What'd she say?
She was better.
I could see her softening.
She didn't use the "D" word.
My eyes, I could see you two
back together within a couple months.
That your honest read?
That's my honest read, Marty.
Look, I don't know
how this guy I'm meeting tonight
feels about me.
What does that mean?
It means if you lose track of me tonight,
keep this fucker handy.
And be listening
to Beaumont police channels.
Yeah.
- You got it?
- Yeah.
- You got it.
- I got it.
Are you gonna be all right?
Crash here for Ginger.
After Houston, I got to
a doc in Eagle Pass.
Coyote got me across the border.
Past two years I've been working security
for a group in San Miguel.
Feds never ID'd me, so I figured,
"Hell, two years pass, things chill down."
It was cool for me to come back,
stick my head out.
It'll be tough, man,
thinking you been dead this whole time.
Fuck, I look dead, motherfucker?
I'm looking to get with you.
You or Miles.
Miles ain't gonna wanna see you, Crash.
Oh, I think he might.
Then I'd say,
I don't think you want to see Miles.
Man, I ain't here to start
a thing, all right.
Boys I been running with in Mexico, there
could be a hell of a deal for both sides.
Fucking money to be made.
Real money.
What kind of money?
Goddamn, Rust.
What the fuck?
My boys are looking to trade' all right?
Coke for meth.
What you got there?
This is something just for you.
- Something just for me'?
- U h-huh.
What'd you cut it with?
You'll see.
You dig it.
After all I meant to you, huh?
Now, who exactly are these guys?
Uh, they...
Ex-Mex army.
They got a Colombian connection.
They need meth for the maquiladoras.
They could cook it themselves,
but then the cartels would take notice,
and that ain't what they're looking for.
Hmm.
Here.
Taste that, homie.
- That ain't no fuck around shit.
- Goddamn.
Whom.!
You keep it.
I got bulldozers' worth of that shit
where I came from.
The thing is,
we got one cook.
Does all our work exclusive, like.
He's real specific about that.
What's this worth to you, Crash?
Me selling Miles on this?
I'll go you one better, brother.
We don't take that shit to Miles at all.
You and me work the supplier.
The cut's whatever the
fuck we want it to be.
Now, that's tricky shit, bro.
And I don't know you like I used to.
I don't know you like I used to either.
That's why the fuck I'm here.
Well, let me tell you why I came, Crash.
I need something from you.
Tonight.
I had a four-man team for a big grab
and lost one to smokies.
I came looking to replace him.
If you're still a badass.
I don't do A and R, man.
No fucking bank job.
It ain't nothing like that.
I need a good soldier.
Now, you do this with us,
we talk about putting you with my man.
Look.
I don't ride cowboy no more, Ginger.
None of this small-time shit like this
thing you're talking about, all right?
What, did you get neutered down south?
I embrace the outlaw life.
Now you dress the part, still.
That's just an act?
When in Rome, brother.
But I do clean up real fucking pretty.
Motherfucker, I need a gunslinger.
Now, you ain't too timid,
get on this shit with me.
Then we can talk about doing business.
Where?
My place.
Down the bayou.
All right, I got my truck.
It'll be safe here.
Members only.
I'm just looking for a friend.
Hey! What the fuck?
Look, look, look. My buddy's in AA...
But you ain't listening.
And I'm his sponsor.
I'm worried that he might
have started drinking again.
You better worry we don't pull your
head off and shit down your neck!
He's been 20 years sober!
Just give me one second!
- What the hell?
- I'm leaving.
A guy could just come in here and say,
"Looking for a fucking friend"!
Get the fuck out of here!
I'm leaving!
Jesus Christ.
Hey, motherfucker!
That's good.
Gotta piss, man!
Fuck is that?
That's Tigger the nigger.
Name's Tiger Thomas.
Dealer in them Heston Projects.
You know them?
It's like them bungalowed,
flat-like joints, right?
Yeah.
They keep a stash house there.
Fucking suck a dick!
Hey, why don't you shut
the fuck up, nigger?
Fuck you!
So y'all gonna take
a stash house in coon country, huh?
Four guys.
How big's the projects, man?
Like square block-wise.
Get the gear, Mitch.
Wait till you see this.
You're gonna love it.
You're going in as cops, huh?
Yeah.
You know where the stash house is?
Tiger's gonna take us there.
You got an exit plan?
Hmm?
Timetable?
Real oops come, then what? Huh?
And you say you're going in
in one fucking car?
Uh-huh.
As far as I remember, man,
place is blocked in.
Now there's one way in, one way out.
It could be fucking Mogadishu, man.
We hit trouble, you just gonna
fuck it in the ass.
You scoop out the soft
brains inside the skull.
So you have thought it out.
My bad.
I come through for you on this tonight,
I gotta know you're gonna hook me up.
'Cause I got a real job
I was supposed to be doing.
Hmm?
You got my word.
You back me on this, I back you.
Fuck it. Let's go.
Up and at 'em, eggplant!
Motherfuckers. Fuck you!
- Come on!
- Fuck you! I'll kill you motherfuckers!
Y'all are dead!
Available cars, possible 503
at the Sears lot in the mall.
40-6 reported on Holyhill Street.
All available 459 at the Circle K,
corner of Lake and Lincoln.
Air three, dispatch.
Go ahead, air three.
Over Zone 6. Heston Projects.
Pretty quiet. Possible 507s.
Everything's code four.
Copy that. 10-4, air three.
I mean
you got two ways to look at it, Tiger.
You can die and lose your shit,
or you could live
and go make some more shit.
Yo, get back
in your house now. Police.
Sheriffs department!
Get back in your house. Do it.
There's nothing to see here.
- You sorry son of a bitch.
- Get the fuck out of here.
Bitches gonna die. You gonna die tonight.
Drop these motherfuckers.
What's up, man? What's this?
- Drop 'em. Put it down!
- Lamar!
Sheriff's department.
- Freeze, motherfucker.
- Come on. Keep marching. Keep marching.
- Ah!
Get up there, big boy. Get on the door.
- Tell 'em to let us in.
- Get the fuck...
Open the door, Lamar!
Tell 'em who you are.
Open the fucking door, Lamar! It's Tiger!
Beat on it!
Everybody down! Now!
Sheriffs! Hands behind your head!
- Get the fuck down!
- No!
Turn that light off, bitch!
Hey' sit the fuck down!
- Where the fuck is it'?
- Sit the fuck down!
You guys
aren't talking, motherfuckers!
Don't move.
It ain't a 5-0, dog.
They don't even have license plates!
Get everybody, man!
Someone gonna get strapped, nigga!
Get in the tub. That's it.
You lay down. Don't you move.
Get me outta here!
Shut your fucking mouth!
Up on the left, man! Right there.
No, no, no. Ginger, no! Don't touch it.
It's in there.
You open it, motherfucker.
I'll put something else in your face.
Get your fucking ass over there!
Start moving! Come on!
Come out, motherfuckers,
we know you in there!
You motherfucker, get
that shit off of there!
- Come on, hurry your ass up!
Motherfucker.
Watch your fucking mouth.
All right, 30 seconds in and out.
Thirty seconds in and out.
Get that safe open!
Watch it! Watch it!
I'll nuke you, motherfucker!
Keep your fucking mouth shut.
- Get the fuck off my dog!
- Take it easy!
Easy. Let's get in
and get the fuck out, Ginger.
Get that light outta my face.
It's Christmastime, Crash!
We got this shit!
Easy. In and out, in and out, in and out.
Somebody looking outside!
Stay calm. Get it, Ginger.
Get the fuck outta here!
Ginger! They are gathering out there!
What the fuck?
- Aah! Come on, Ginger!
- They're animals out there, man!
Easy' easy.
- Easy, motherfucker.
- Shut your motherfucking mouth.
Thirty seconds. Hold 'em down.
- Ginger, let's fucking go!
- They got guns!
You sorry yet, motherfucker?
I told your cracker-ass...
Do not fire. Don't fucking fire!
Do not fire.
No! Lamar! Lamar!
Ginger, Ginger! Stop fucking around!
Fuck you!
The fuck?
Fuck me.
What the fuck?
Ginger!
I fucking knew it!
I wish I could have done this from
the start, you fucking moron!
Fuck! Fuck! What the fuck
are you doing, man?
Shut the fuck up!
Freeze!
- Who else is in the house?
- Nobody.
Get in the bathroom.
Get in the bathroom! Lay down.
Marty. Okay, I need you to be at Amelia
Street between 18th and 19th in 90 seconds.
You got it? You got it?
Amelia! 18th and 19th!
Ninety seconds, motherfucker!
There's one right there.
There goes another one!
Get your ass up! Come on!
Ginger!
You stupid motherfucker.
They're fucking everywhere, man!
Keep going, man! Come on!
Hurry up, man!
Put your weapon down!
- You motherfucker. You rat bitch.
- Shut the fuck up.
You'll get yours, fucking Crash,
you motherfucker.
Come outwith your hands raised.
Get on your knees!
They shooting down up at Tiger's.
They shot up Tiger house.
- Who?
- The police. Load up!
Let's go! Let's go!
The police just shot up Tiger house.
Fucking dark. Here.
Oh, shit!
Hey!
Go! Go!
Go, go, go!
What the fuck happened?
I need that contact. Now.
You rat motherfucker.
You give me that location for Ledoux,
I'm gonna let you slide, Ginger.
Bullshit.
What the fuck do you think
I want with you, huh?
Goddamn, I am so done
talking to you like a man.
Go, go, go.